[
  {
    "front": "Good morning",
    "back": "Buenos días"
  },
  {
    "front": "Good afternoon",
    "back": "Buenas tardes"
  },
  {
    "front": "Good night",
    "back": "Buenas noches"
  },
  {
    "front": "How are you?",
    "back": "¿Cómo estás?"
  },
  {
    "front": "Very well",
    "back": "Muy bien"
  },
  {
    "front": "Thank you!",
    "back": "¡Gracias!"
  },
  {
    "front": "No problem!",
    "back": "¡De nada!"
  },
  {
    "front": "Please",
    "back": "Por favor"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sorry!",
    "back": "¡Lo siento!"
  },
  {
    "front": "Do you understand?",
    "back": "¿Entiende?"
  },
  {
    "front": "Yes",
    "back": "Sí"
  },
  {
    "front": "No",
    "back": "No"
  }
]
